Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive, 1989-2004 MSS.191
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XXIV: Organizational Digital Data Storage
  - Red Hot Minis, 1990-1996; cuid8633; SyQuest 44 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0014)
    This item has been separated from Series XIXA, Box 28, folder 13.